findwith.me 2017-06-24

# Privacy :: Findwith.me :: Whatever you're looking for, wherever you are

### Policy Privacy

Respecting users' privacy is a key value for Findwith.me. To learn about what personal information Findwith.me collects and how it may be used, please read Findwith.me's privacy policy here below. If you have any questions, please send an email to [info@findwith.me](mailto:info@findwith.me). Thank you.

We will comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 and any other applicable data protection legislation. By registering for the Findwith.me Services you consent to our using and/or disclosing your personal information for the following purposes:

  * providing, or arranging for third parties to provide, help desk facilities which may be available to you which may involve disclosing your personal information to third parties solely for those purposes;
  * providing, or arranging for third parties - including third parties located not within the European Union - to provide, any additional services you request from us;
  * as required or permitted by law from time to time.

We will not use your personal data for marketing other Findwith.me products and services or any third party products and services without having given you the opportunity to opt out of such marketing opportunities.

We are committed to protecting your right to privacy. Any information you provide to us will be held on computers that are based in the European Union orin the United States of America. We collect information about our users in order to help continually improve the Findwith.me Services. We also use the information you provide us to enter into commercial arrangements, including the sale of advertising space, which allow the Findwith.me Service to remain free for all our users. We will always adhere to the Data Protection Act 1998 (UK) in relation to our use of your information and any other applicable data protection laws. This Privacy Policy relates only to our use of the information you provide us and your use of the Findwith.me Website and does not extend to your use of the Internet other than the Findwith.me Website.

### What data do we collect from you?

We use cookie technology to monitor which areas of the Findwith.me Website you prefer. The information obtained from the cookies is not stored alongside your personal data and will only be used on an anonymous, aggregated basis. We may also hold information relating to any transactions that you enter into with us or any of our third party retail partners.

We use the advertising agencies to serve ads when you visit Findwith.me Websites. These companies may use information about your visits to Findwith.me Websites, including the searches you conduct while on Findwith.me Websites. None of this information is used to identify you personally. This information is used to present you with relevant advertisements on other Websites that you may visit.

### What we do with the data we collect from you?

We may use the personal information we collect from you to build up a profile of your interests and preferences.

### Third Party Advertising

The advertisements appearing on the Findwith.me Website are delivered to you by ourselves and by third parties such as Google Ireland Limited.,Yahoo Sarl and Ask.com. Information about your visit to the Findwith.me Website, such as the number of times you have viewed a particular advertisement (but not information about you, such as your name, address or any other personal information) is used to decide which advertisements to serve to you.

In the course of serving advertisements to you cookie technology may be used, but such cookies will not be used to collect any personally identifiable information about you.

### Private Communications

It is our policy to respect the privacy of private communications. We will not intentionally inspect the contents of private communications sent or received using the Findwith.me Portal except as required or permitted to do so by law.

### Disclosure of data in accordance with law

We may need to disclose your data to appropriate persons where required or permitted by law (for example, to law enforcement authorities in relation to the investigation of a suspected criminal offence).

### Changing contact details

If you have any questions about the use of your personal data please contact us at:

YOUniversal Next Limited  
51/52 Fitzwilliam Square W - Dublin 2  
EIRE  
Email: [info@findwith.me](mailto:info@findwith.me)

### Changes to the Policy

We may need to amend the Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such amendment will take effect as soon as it is posted on the Findwith.me Website. You are therefore encouraged to familiarise yourself with the Privacy Policy on a regular basis. The Privacy Policy will always be easily accessible online throughout Findwith.me Website.
